Meki-chan, Meki-chan.
めきちゃん、めきちゃん
long time no see.
久しぶり
Wow, you're seriously wearing a uniform.
え、マジで制服着てきてくれてんじゃん
That's right.
そうだよね
Congratulations, you graduated.
おめでとう、卒業
thank you.
ありがとう
cute?
かわいい?
cute.
かわいい
It's so cute.
めちゃくちゃかわいい
thank you.
ありがとう
Will you buy me some food?
ご飯をおごってくれるの
Oh, rice?
あ、ご飯?
I took the trouble to bring him a uniform.
せっかく制服着てきてあげたんだから
That's right.
そうだよね
Sorry.
ごめんね
Rice, is that yakiniku?
ご飯、あれ、焼肉か
I want yakiniku.
焼肉いたいんだよね
An expensive one.
高いやつ
That's expensive.
高いやつね
Okay, leave me alone.
オッケー、任しといて
Today, what shall we do?
今日さ、じゃあさ、どうしようか
I'll go take a photo if you try a little harder.
撮影じゃあちょっと頑張ってくれたら行こうか
real?
ほんと?
Yeah.
うん
For a graduation gift.
卒業祝いにね
I did it.
やった
So, did you get a boyfriend?
あれ、彼氏できた?
still.
まだ
still?
まだ?
Yeah.
うん
Hey, that's right.
へ ー、そうだよね
That's right, why aren't you here all the time?
そうだよねっていうか、なんでずっといないの?
Don't you have it?
つくんないの?
I wonder why.
なんでだろう
Hey, Meki-chan, you still smell great.
てかさ、めきちゃんさ、相変わらずいい匂いすんね
real?
ほんと?
It always smells like something naughty.
なんかエッチな匂いがずーっとするんだよね
why?
なんで?
Don't write.
書かないで
cute.
かわいい
It's so cute.
めっちゃかわいいね
thank you.
ありがとう
Wait a minute, Miki-chan.
ちょっとさ、じゃあみきちゃんさ、
Do you want to take a walk?
散歩する?
Yeah.
うん
Okay.
いいよ
Shall we take a walk?
散歩しようか
And now, today, you can kind of understand, right?
そしてさ、今日さ、ちょっとさ、ある程度分かるでしょ?
It's just something to do.
なんかやることっていうのはさ
roughly?
大体?
That's about it.
大体だよね
So what do you say?
だからさ、なんていうの?
I thought I'd like to have some naughty fun,
ちょっとエッチな遊びしたいなと思ってさ、
In this park.
この公園で
Hey, wait a minute.
ねー、やだちょっと
No?
やだ?
No, it's embarrassing.
やだよね、恥ずかしいよね
There are a lot of them.
いっぱいいるしね
Just a little bit?
ちょっとだけ?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけの
good?
いい?
How about getting a remote control?
リモコン仕込むぐらい?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけね
Should I just do it for a little while?
ちょっとだけでやったらいい?
OK
Well then, let's go to a place where I can get a remote control.
じゃあちょっと、リモコン仕込める場所行こうかな
good?
いい?
Miki-chan, if it's here, I can probably prepare it.
み きちゃん、ここだったらさ、多分仕込みできるよ
good?
いい?
Is it okay if I install a remote bike?
リモバイ仕込んじゃっていい?
Got it.
分かった
good?
いい?
Hey, before that, give me a service short.
ちょっとさ、その前にさ、サービスショートちょうだい
Hey, are you hiding it?
ほら、隠してんの?
Can I have you spread your legs a little bit?
ちょっと足広げてもらっていい?
Oh, I want to see your pants.
あ、パンツ見たいな
cute.
かわいい
My mange is growing properly.
ちゃんとまんげ生えてんじゃん
cute.
か わいい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよね
That's right.
そうだよ
sorry.
ごめん
It's outside.
外だよ
That's right.
そうだよね
Sorry.
ごめんね
Then, come on, take your pants off.
そしたらさ、じゃあさ、 パンツずらしてよ
Oh, my gosh.
あ、やべ
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
The security guard is on the move.
警備員さんが動いてる
Ah, it seems okay.
あ、大丈夫っぽい
Are you going to get caught?
捕まっちゃお?
Ah, he's gone.
あ、いなくなった
He's gone.
いなくなった
OK、OK
Then, can I move your pants a little?
そしたらじゃあ、ちょっとパンツずらしていい?
Does it match?
合ってる?
I'll go for a while.
ちょっといってくよ
cute.
かわいい
Yes, then hold it down with your pants.
はい、じゃあパンツで押さえて
OK
good?
いい?
Go all the way to the back.
ちゃんと奥まで行って
Did you do it?
できた?
Yes, preparation is complete.
はい、仕込み完了しました
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
It feels a little strange.
ちょっと変な感じ
Does it feel a little strange?
ちょっと変な感じする?
It feels a little strange.
ちょっと変な感じするよね
Well then, let's go for a walk outside.
ちょっとじゃあそれでさ、 外歩いてみようかな
I want to go for a walk.
散歩したいなそれで
Just a little.
ちょっとだけだよ
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけだよね
Got it.
分かった
good?
いい?
Miki-chan, the preparation is complete.
みきちゃん、仕込み完了したね
Well then, Miki-chan, viewers.
じゃあみきちゃんさ、視聴者さんがさ、
After all, what do you say?
やっぱりさ、なんていうの
I don't know anything about Miki-chan.
俺はさ、みきちゃんのこと知ってんじゃん
It's been a long time.
昔からさ
The viewers probably don't know, after all.
視聴者さんはさ、やっぱ知らないじゃん、
so.
そんなに
There's a lot going on here, so let's listen to the demo while listening to it.
いろいろちょっとそこでさ、デモ映えしながらちょっと聞いていき
I think so.
たい なと思うんだけどさ
Got it.
分かった
Okay.
いいよ
First of all, it looks a little like a demo,
まずさ、ちょっとデモ映えちょっと、
Now that it's true, let's do it.
本当になってるから、じゃあちょっとやるね
Are you coming?
来てる?
It's coming.
来てる
Are you coming?
来てる?
Is that what I expected?
やっぱあれ?
Do you fidget?
もじもじしちゃう?
That's right.
だよね
Miki-chan, you're fidgeting.
みきちゃんさ、 もじもじしてんね
Miki-chan, you said you don't have a boyfriend.
みきちゃんさ、彼氏いないって言ってたじゃん
How long have you been gone?
どんくらいいないの?
About 2 years.
2年くらい
About 2 years?
2年くらい?
Yeah.
うん
Well then, what?
え、じゃあさ、何?
Huh?
あれ?
Maybe.
もしかして
Yeah.
うん
Okay, that's when we met.
いい、あれさ、俺とさ、出会った頃さ、
You were dragging it out a bit, Miki-chan.
ちょっと引きずってたじゃん、みきちゃん
Um, um, that was the last one.
あの、あの、あれが最後の
That's the last one.
あれ最後だよ
Oh, seriously?
あ、マジで?
Seriously?
マジか?
Yeah.
うん
cute.
かわいい
Is it okay to fidget like that?
そんなもじもじしちゃって大丈夫?
Strong.
強くて
Strong?
強くて?
Because it's strong.
強いから
It's strong, isn't it?
強いよね
It's crazy, he's fidgeting so much.
やばいじゃん、すごいもじもじしてるよ
I'm so surprised.
びっくびっくしちゃう
That's right.
そうだよね
It's full, there will be a lot of people from now on,
いっぱいだってさ、これからいっぱい人いるけど、
Is it okay?
大丈夫かな?
Hmm, that's embarrassing.
う ーん、恥ずかしい
Oh, it's a little painful to look at.
あら、ちょっと視線痛いですね
It hurts a little.
ちょっと痛い
cute.
かわいい
What, aren't you going to university?
え、大学は行かないの?
Are you going?
行くの?
Yeah, I'll go.
うん、行く
Are you going?
行くの?
Yeah.
うん
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Wait a minute, then let's go over here.
ちょっと待って、じゃあちょっとこっち行く
Did you enjoy high school?
高校楽しかった?
It was fun.
楽しかったよ
What did you enjoy?
何が楽しかった?
number one.
一番
Hmm, I guess I went out with a friend after all.
う ーん、やっぱ友達と一緒に出かかったかな
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
I have a lot of female friends.
女友達多いもんね
There are a lot of them.
いっぱいいる
いっぱいいるよね
I see, that old man is just a little...
そっか、あれさ、おじさんはさ、ちょっとさ、
I don't know, maybe it's the sports festival.
分かんないんだけどさ、 体育祭だったりさ、
What do you mean?
なんていうの?
What is it, a wedding festival?
なんだっけ、婚楽祭?
Is that an event type?
そういうイベント系?
Was it really interesting?
やっぱ面白かった?
It was fun.
楽しかったよ
It was fun, wasn't it?
楽しかったよね
Oh, what, do you still have a vibrator?
あら、まだ何、バイブあんの?
Are you being messed with in various ways?
いろいろいじられちゃってる?
full.
いっぱい
Are you being messed with a lot?
い っぱいいじられちゃってる?
Ever since now.
さ っきからずっと
yes?
そう?
Has he been messing with you ever since?
さっきからずっといじられちゃってる?
That's right.
そうだよね
Like this,
こんなさ、
A beautiful, cute girl was walking in a park like this.
き れいなかわいい女の子がこんな公園で歩いてた
I can only wear something special.
おもばいしか着られて
It's tough.
大変だね
It's true.
本当だよ
本当だよね
But I said it's okay if it's just a little bit.
だけどちょっとだけだったらいいって言ったもんね
I said just a little.
ちょっとだけって言った
I'm still doing it.
まだやってるんだもんね
I'm still wearing it.
まだ着けてるの
まだ着けてる
I want to get off early.
早く降りたい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Give me a little more.
もうちょっとちょうだいよ
Let's try a little harder.
あともうちょっとがんばろう
I can't walk well.
上手に歩けない
Can't walk well?
上手に歩けない?
I can't walk well.
上手に歩けないよね
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
I can't walk well.
上手に歩けないよね
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Okay.
いいよ
I feel like a child with a stomach ache.
なんかお腹が痛い子みたい
I want to see it from around me.
周りからみたい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
恥ずかしいよね
It's embarrassing.
but...
でも...
Do you want it to stop?
もうやめてほしい?
It's embarrassing too...
恥ずかしいのも...
Well, once, just once, once, if there's a little break.
じゃあ一回さ、ちょっとさ、一回じゃあちょっと休憩があったら
May I?
いい ですか?
Ah, let's sit on the bench.
あー、ベンチ座ろうか
As far as sitting on the bench, then just a little bit.
ベンチ座るところまでさ、 じゃあちょっとさ、
Shall we go?
行こうか
good?
いい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよね
It's like this.
こんなのね
But I guess it feels good.
でもちょっと気持ちいいかな
Naughty.
エッチ
Very naughty.
すごいエッチ
Stop it.
やめてよ
Miki-chan is so naughty.
みきちゃんめちゃくちゃエッチじゃん
It's so naughty.
すごいエッチじゃん
Haven't you had sex?
セックスしてないの?
recently.
最近
I haven't done it at all.
全然してない
That's right.
そうだよね
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
That thing just got stronger.
さっきあれ強くなった
Have you become stronger?
強くなった?
There's no bench.
ベンチないね
Where is it?
どこある?
bench.
ベンチ
I'd like to find a bench.
ベンチ探したいんだけどさ
Hey, Miki-chan, why don't you show me your naughty side?
ちょっとさ、 みきちゃんのさ、 ちょっとエッチな姿見せたら
Well, uncle, I'm starting to feel naughty.
さ、 ちょっとおじさま、 エッチな気分になってきちゃった
Really.
本当に
Well then, let's have a lot.
じゃあ、いっぱいしよう
Can I fill it up?
いっぱいしていいの?
So cute, really.
可愛い、本当に
That's naughty.
エッチだね
Because there were people.
人がいたからさ
Come here for a moment.
ちょっとこっちおいで
Just sit here and poop.
ちょっとここでさ、 うんこ座りしてみて
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It's moving.
動いてる
I can hear it, fine.
音聞こえます、ちゃんと
I can hear the sound clearly.
しっかりちゃんと音聞こえてます
It's intense.
激しいね
Wow, I'm getting a little excited.
やばい、ちょっと興奮してきちゃった
I want to go to a hotel.
ホテル行きたいな
Just for a little while before going to the hotel.
ちょっとだけどホテル行く前にさ、
I might not be able to stand it for a while.
ちょっと我慢できないかも
Should it be here?
ここだったらいい?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
here.
ここ
There's a few people over there.
ちょっと人いるよ、あそこに
There are, right?
いるよね
But, maybe, I can't watch it.
だけどさ、たぶんだけど、 見られなくない?
I couldn't stand it anymore.
よりちょっと我慢できなくなっちゃった
Then I'll stop when people come.
じゃあ人来たらやめる
Stop, stop.
やめるやめる
I'll stop when people come.
人来たらやめる
Ah, but there are a few people.
あ、だけどちょっと人いるね
I'm watching you.
見てるね
But, can I force my way through?
だけど、強行突破していいかな?
Understood.
わかった
good?
いい?
Yeah.
うん
It has big hands.
大きい手になっている
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
For a moment, it continued.
ちょっとさ、 続きた
Shall we put it in the car?
車の中にしようか
Yeah.
うん
I was surprised just now.
さ っきびっくりしたね
It's true.
本当だよ
Sorry, sorry.
ごめんごめん
No, there was a real parent and child.
いや、ガチ親子いた
And he was a very small child.
しかもめちゃくちゃちっちゃい子だったから
It's no good if they see it.
見られたらダメだもん
Sorry, seriously.
ごめんね、まじで
That's why I evacuated.
だから避難してきた
But I'm glad I didn't find out.
でもよかった、ばれなくて
It hasn't been revealed.
ばれてない
Maybe, because we were apart for a moment.
たぶんね、離れてったから一瞬
Maybe they found out, but we'll never see each other again.
たぶんばれたんだけど、 もう二度と会わないじゃん
It was discovered.
ばれちゃったもん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Just a little bit, yeah, yeah.
ちょっとさ、 そうそうそう
Right foot?
右足か
Can I have it raised?
上 げてもらっていい?
Cute and erotic.
かわいい、エロ
Wait a minute, can I do it?
ちょっとじゃあ、 やっていい?
Oh, erotic.
あら、エロ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
Moreover, if you look at it in a bright place,
しかもさ、 明るいところで見たらさ、
My mange is growing properly.
ちゃんとまんげ生えてるんよね
I don't know what to do.
どうしていいか分かんなくて
Erotic and cute.
エロ、かわいい
Well then, hey, can I continue?
じゃあ さ、ちょっとさ、 続きしていい?
earlier.
さっきの
continuation?
続き?
Can I continue with the erotica?
エロの続きしていい?
good?
いい?
He's such a good kid.
めちゃくちゃいい子じゃん
Well then, before you change your mind,
じゃあ さ、 気が変わんないうちにさ、
I'm going to the hotel now, so I'll leave it for now.
ホテルさ、 今から行くからさ、 この間までさ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
mother,
お母さん、
I want to do it quickly.
早 くやっちゃいたい
Do you want to do it?
やっちゃいたい?
I have to get to the hotel soon.
早くホテルつかないと、 ちょっと、
I might go for a while.
ちょっと行っちゃうかもしれない
Hotel Tsukushi is a bit dangerous,
ホテルつくし、 ちょっとやばいから、
Let's give it a try.
ちょっとやってみよう
Mi-chan, are you okay?
みーちゃん、大丈夫?
Yeah.
うん
Okay, okay.
いいよ、いいよ
It's Tatsuki Hotel.
タツキホテルですよ
Mi-chan.
みーちゃん
what?
何?
I couldn't take it anymore so I came to the hotel.
我慢できなくなったからホテル来ちゃったよ
I was brought here.
連れてこられちゃった
You've been brought here.
連れてこられちゃったね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Really.
本当に
Finally.
やっとだよ
I've finally come this far.
やっとここまで来たわ
It's fun to go and do it.
できに行く楽しいんです
Oh, really?
あ、本当に?
You haven't forgotten yet.
まだ忘れてなかったね
I haven't forgotten.
忘れてないよ
It's a promise.
約束だもん
That's right.
そうだよね
I'll take you there properly.
ちゃんと連れて行ってあげるから
Got it.
分かった
I agree.
そうだね
I'll bring you some yakiniku,
焼肉はちゃんと連れて行くから、
Let's enjoy sex today.
今日は セックス楽しもう
Got it.
分かった
There's no point in talking too much.
あんまり喋ってても、 しょうがないじゃん
Well, you can't stand it.
だ し、 我慢できないでしょ
Yeah.
うん
Right?
でしょ?
Isn't that true?
そんなことない?
Is there such a thing?
そんなことある?
a little bit.
ちょっと
It's cute.
かわいいね
Well then, let's do it now.
じゃあもうやっちゃおうか
It felt far away.
遠く感じた
I don't think I'll manipulate it.
操かないかなと
Isn't it Yakiniku in your head?
頭の中焼肉なんじゃない?
That's not true.
そんなことない
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I need to get hungry before I eat.
食べる前にお腹減らさないとね
As expected.
さすがに
Se
セ
Ikon, it suits you.
イ コン、似合ってるね
Yeah.
うん
I just graduated a while ago.
もう前、卒業したばかりじゃん
Seems like a nice station.
いい駅みたい
I have to come now.
もう来ちゃいけないんだよ
Can't go?
行けないの?
It's Prasley.
プラズリーじゃん
That's a pretty face.
きれいな顔だね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
already.
もう
Show me your body.
体見せて
Slowly move clockwise and have them show you their butts.
ゆっくり時計回りに お尻見せてもらう
Have it raised.
上げてもらう
Spread your arms out and show me what's inside your head.
両手で広げて、 頭の中見せて
Please show me the camera.
ちゃんとカメラ見せてあげて
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
恥ずかしいね
Don't hide it with your hands.
手で隠しちゃダメだよ
Are you spreading it out properly?
ちゃん と広げてる?
Doesn't it spread?
広がらない?
Next, spread it out.
次、広げてほら
Don't spread.
広がらないで